pdaphonehome.com 2008-06-03

# PDAPhoneHome.com - Privacy Policy

|  |  **Home of the Converged PDA - Phone** |   |   |   
---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  **» Current Poll**  
---  
Do you like my Special Edition Burberry i760  
YES  
NO  
  
» [View Poll Results](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/samsung-sch-i760/poll-569-do-you-like-my-special-edition-burberry-i760.html)

» [Discuss This Poll](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/newreply.php?t=111357)

» [This Poll Has 10 Replies](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/samsung-sch-i760/111357-what-do-you-guys-think-my-skin.html)  
  
**» Site Navigation**  
---  
  
» Default / Homepage

 > Advertising

 > House Rules

 > PDAPhone Information

  > Device Specs Page

 > Learn - TEST

  > Sony Ericsson P900

  > PPC-6600 / XV-6600

  > Samsung SPH-i700

  > Treo 755P

  > Apple iPhone

  > PPC-6700 / XV-6700

  > T-Mobile Pocket PC Phone Edition

  > Sony Ericsson P800

  > Treo 600

  > Treo 650

  > Treo 700P

  > Samsung SPH-i500

  > T-Mobile Dash

  > Samsung SCH-i730

  > Kyocera 7135

  > Samsung SCH-i760

  > Cingular Blackjack / Samsung SGH-i607

 > Learn

 > **Privacy Policy**

» testnav

» tabletest

» Where Are You Going

» test page

» PDAPhoneHome News Archive  
  
**» June 2008**  
---  
S | M | T | W | T | F | S  
1  |  2  |  3  |  4  |  5  |  6  |  7   
8  |  9  |  10  |  11  |  12  |  13  |  14   
15  |  16  |  17  |  18  |  19  |  20  |  21   
22  |  23  |  24  |  25  |  26  |  27  |  28   
29  |  30  | 1| 2| 3| 4| 5  
  
**» Advertiser**  
---  
  
|   
  
**» Today's Birthdays**  
---  
[DJDoctaDawe](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/djdoctadawe.html) (88)  
[Robin Tuchler](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/robin-tuchler.html) (64)  
[DSG](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/dsg.html) (61)  
[LeifEn](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/leifen.html) (57)  
[jpdsr51](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/jpdsr51.html) (57)  
[leeh](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/leeh.html) (49)  
[triyoni](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/triyoni.html) (48)  
[bostonkarl](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/bostonkarl.html) (46)  
[95stealthtt](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/95stealthtt.html) (43)  
[mechintl](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/mechintl.html) (43)  
[iugalde](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/iugalde.html) (42)  
[Keen](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/keen.html) (38)  
[comanch3](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/comanch3.html) (37)  
[d-dawg](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/d-dawg.html) (36)  
[sbono13](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/sbono13.html) (35)  
[ssoggy](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/ssoggy.html) (35)  
[sdjernes](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/sdjernes.html) (32)  
[buffy](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/members/buffy.html) (31)   
  
**»[Online Users: 781](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/online.php)**  
---  
31 members and 750 guests  
Most users ever online was 2605, 03-10-2008 at 03:24 PM.  
  
**»[Search Forums](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/search.php)**  
---  
  
» [Advanced Search](http://pdaphonehome.com/forums/search.php)  
  
|  **» Privacy Policy**  
---  
|  **pdaPhoneHome Privacy Policy**  
---  
This policy applies to the **pdaPhoneHome** web site and only webpages that contain the http://pdaphonehome.com url. You may find inportant information about safe web surfing at the [**Federal Trade Commission Website**](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm). If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at [webmaster@pdaphonehome.com](mailto:webmaster@pdaphonehome.com).   
  
* * *  
  
**Information Collection and Use**  

  * pdaPhoneHome collects personal information when you register with pdaPhoneHome, when you complete some online pdaPhoneHome surveys, when you purchase products from the pdaPhoneHome store, when you purchase products from pdaPhoneHome Affiliates, and when you enter promotions. We may combine information about you that we have collected with information we obtain from pdaPhoneHome Affiliates.
  * When you register at pdaPhoneHome we ask for information such as your name, email address, instant messaging addresses, personal website url, birth date, gender, location, occupation, and personal interests.
  * When you purchase products from the pdaPhoneHome store or pdaPhoneHome Affiliate stores, we may also ask for your name, address, telephone number, credit card or other payment information.
  * Once you register with pdaPhoneHome and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * pdaPhoneHome collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. pdaPhoneHome automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, operating system, pdaPhoneHome cookie information, and the page you request. If you do not register with pdaPhoneHome, or purchase products, this is the only information we collect.
  * pdaPhoneHome uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve the content of our web pages, contact you about promotions and updates to the website, conduct research, and to provide statistical analysis for our own use. We do not share the information we collect with any other organizations.

* * *  
  
**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * pdaPhoneHome does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or other companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under special circumstances such as legal proceedings and investigations, or mergers.
  * pdaPhoneHome uses ad servers and ad server companies to bring you advertising that may be of interest to you. As a result of your visit to our site, the ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. The ad server companies may also collect personal information from you when you interact with the other linked sites. You should refer to the privacy policies of the ad server companies and the other linked sites to determine how your personal information is handled. pdaPhoneHome will provide a list of the ad server companies being used upon request. The ad server companies used may change without notice.

* * *  
  
**Cookies**  

  * pdaPhoneHome may set and access pdaPhoneHome cookies on your computer to record session data. 
  * pdaPhoneHome lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. 
  * Advertisers or other companies do not have access to pdaPhoneHome's cookies.

* * *  
  
**Your Ability to Edit / Delete Personal Information**  

  * You can edit your pdaPhoneHome personal information at any time by accessing your user profile page (registered users only).
  * New categories of personal information may be added to the profile page from time to time.
  * pdaPhoneHome reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the pdaPhoneHome website without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Your email address is not made available to any other companies for use in mailings. It is possible for other pdaPhoneHome users to access your email address and send private email.
  * You can delete your pdaPhoneHome account by visiting sending a written request to the email address above.

* * *  
  
**Confidentiality and Security**  

  * We limit access to personal information about you to users with administrator privaledges only.
  * All personal data is stored in a relational database and password protected. Only the site administrators have access to the tools and passwords required to access the data outside of the website.
  * We have taken industry standard means to provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.
  * Your pdaPhoneHome personal information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas of the pdaPhoneHome site, industry-standard SSL-encryption is used to protect data transmissions.

* * *  
  
**Changes to This Policy**  

  * pdaPhoneHome may update this policy without notice. 
  * In the event of a major change to this policy, pdaPhoneHome may post a notification in the site news on the pdaPhoneHome home page.

* * *
